你能想象身处难以置信的环境中的自己吗？
Have you ever found yourself in such as a real situation that you can hardly believe it's real?
我现在就和两位朋友坐在上百吨爆炸物上，准备前往太空
I'm currently sitting on top of tons of explosives with two great friends ready to be shot into space
即人类最大的火箭之一——阿丽亚娜五号
by one of humankind's biggest rockets: the mighty Ariane 5.
真是不错的一天呀
Perfectly normal day, right?
我是Bepi，上面一起的是Mio
I'm Bepi and together with Mio up there
我们将在内太阳系进行一次伟大的旅程，最终前往水星
We're going on a great adventure through the inner solar system to planet Mercury
当然，也不能忘了我们的朋友MTM
But let's not forget about our robot friend MTM
他将负责在星箭分离后带我们一路前往水星
who after this ride on the rocket is going to carry us all the way there.
这次旅程将花费七年，一路飞跃其他行星数次
A journey that will take seven years flying past other planets along the way
我们选水星的目的不是因为那是什么旅游胜地
We certainly didn't pick Mercury because it's the most hospitable destination out there
而是因为那里有很多未解之谜等着我们去解决
but because there are still so many unsolved questions about this mysterious world.
我们一生都在为此次旅行做准备
Our whole lives have been spent getting ready for this great adventure
在学校里，老师们因材施教，让我们扬长避短
We worked very hard in school each bringing our own contribution to the mission
虽然只有我和Mio要去探索水星的未解之谜
Even though it will just be me and Mio investigating Mercury's mysteries.
但我们要靠MTM才能去水星
It will be up to MTM to get us there
没有他可靠的发动机我们根本飞不了那么远
We would not get far without our trusty engine
同样，我们的老师在让我们准备发射前往水星的路途上也功不可没
The same is true for all of our teachers getting us ready for launch and our journey towards the Sun
水星那会很热，就像披萨烤箱一样
It's going to be very hot at times, like working in a pizza oven
MTM和我要穿上特别的衣服来防止晒伤
MTM and I needed to get special jackets fitted to protect us.
而Mio则有更新奇的方法防止在水星过热
Well, Mio invented a novel way to keep cool once at Mercury
她会不停自转来均匀接受来自太阳的热
She's going to spin around to evenly distribute the sun's heat,
但在路上，她会一直呆在一个太阳罩内
but on the way, she will have to sit still inside a Sun shield
除了数学、物理和各种工程知识
As well as math, physics and engineering
我们还要学习各自的语言
We also started to learn each other's languages
Mio来自日本，对欧洲的各个国家和语言充满好奇
Mio is from Japan and is very curious about all the different countries and languages in Europe
而我也在学习日语
while I try to learn some Japanese
我们慢慢开始了解彼此文化的差异
We began to understand some of the differences between our cultures
这对我们未来几年的共同旅行、工作非常重要
which is important because we will spend many years traveling and working together
整个旅途中我们还要进行很多轨道机动，这是要练习很多次的
Throughout the journey we will need to make a lot of manoeuvres and these had to be practiced over and over
我们将飞跃地球一次、金星两次、水星六次，最终环绕水星
We will fly by Earth once, Venus twice and even Mercury six times before orbiting around it
想象一下，我们将是人类第一个同时探索水星的两个探测器
Just imagine, we will be the first mission to study planet Mercury with two spacecraft at the same time
两个好朋友将一起进行很多伟大的实验
Two friends planning to do some great experiments together.
我曾对我未来的旅程满怀憧憬，但我也承认我还是有点害怕的
I was always fascinated by our destination, but I confess I used to be a bit afraid of it
如此刁钻的轨道与离太阳的咫尺之遥让此次旅程犹如刀山火海
Such an odd orbit and being so close to the Sun made it really difficult to get to
水星是内太阳系探索得最少的行星
It was the least explored planet in the inner solar system
但那一晚，一切都变了
But one night changed everything
我突然克服了我的恐惧，甚至深深着迷于此
I quickly overcame my fears and became completely captivated
着迷于我将来的旅程——那将是几乎不曾有探测器涉足过的地方
by the thought of travelling to this strange world that so few spacecraft had braved before
我等不及要亲眼看看那个世界，想了解那里为什么和地球与众不同
I couldn't wait to see it with my own eyes and to understand why it was so different to Earth
在我们渐渐长大的时候，表亲信使号传回了水星很多有趣的发现
As we were growing up our cousin Messenger sent back news of many interesting discoveries on Mercury
反而让我们更加好奇！
Which left us quite curious!
我对撞击坑的火山喷发与构造活动等地质过程很感兴趣
I'm really interested in geological processes like Impact cratering Volcanic eruptions and tectonic activity
以及其如何在数十亿年来改变了行星表面的化学组成和地貌
and how that changes the chemistry and appearance of a planet's surface over billions of years
Mio最喜欢研究磁场和宇宙射线
Mio's favorite subjects are magnetic fields and space plasmas
以及太阳如何影响行星所处的环境
and studying how the Sun influences the planet's environment.
这实际上算是我们的共同目标
That's actually something we're both going to do.
——从不同角度去探索太阳风如何与行星磁场相互作用
Investigate how the solar wind interacts with a planet's magnetic field from our two different viewpoints.
水星是如此赤裸裸的星球，我们将研究太阳和小型陨石
Mercury is a rather exposed planet and we would be able to see how the Sun and small meteorites
如何改变水星表面和我们轨道周围环境的
change the conditions both down there and in the environment along our orbits.
我相信我们将看到很多改变，我们也很兴奋能同心协力
It certainly sounded like we would see lots of changes and we were excited to bring our skills together
以一个完整的系统来让我们更好地了解水星
to better understand the planet as a complete system.
有无数未解之谜在等待着我们
There are certainly still plenty of mysteries to solve
是时候出发啦
It's almost time to go